carrotsncake.com 2019-07-18

# Privacy Policy - Carrots 'N' Cake

Last updated: May 7, 2019

Carrots 'N' Cake (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the Carrots 'N' Cake website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://carrotsncake.com

## Vistors

I use a number of methods to see how you interact with Carrots ‘N’ Cake. I do this to improve the website and content for you. In doing so, I track specific visitors who visit my site, track the pages you visit on my site, and the websites you came from. This information is for me to improve and better Carrots ‘N’ Cake. Statistics may be shared publicly, but personal information on my visitors is never shared.

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, enter information on our site, or simply browsing the site.

We may collect personal information from you that you’ve voluntarily submitted to us, such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to this website when signing up for newsletters or submitting a comment or submitting an inquiry via our contact form.

We may also collect anonymous information such as your IP address. Anonymous information consists of non-personally-identifiable data. For example, when you use our website, we can log your IP address, the device you are using, operating system, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, time spent on our site, when you came to our site. We may also collect information on actions you take while visiting our website, such as what links or buttons you clicked on.

## Cookies

Carrots ‘N’ Cake may use cookies & tracking technologies depending on the features offered. Cookies and tracking technologies are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to this site, a visitor’s demographics, and understanding how visitors use this site.

Cookies are also to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved user-experience. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since everyone’s browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, it won’t affect your user-experience.

You may have also subscribed to our newsletter. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of our marketing campaign. These tracking pixels allow us to see when you opened the email, if you opened the email, and what links you clicked in the email. This also allows the website to adapt future newsletter content to the interest of the user. This behavior is strictly confidential and will not be passed onto third parties.

## Email Subscribers

On Carrots ‘N’ Cake you can opt to enter your email address to receive website updates on recent posts. I will never send you spam messages or give out your email address. I do not sell, trade, or transfer any personal information to outside parties. When you correspond with us through email, your email address and the contents of the email is retained. We provide the same protections for these emails as we employ in all information that we have received electronically.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from all correspondence.

## Third Party Disclosure

Some of our advertisers may use technology such as cookies when they advertise on our site. The advertiser’s technology can send these advertisers information that may be contained in log files. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

Display Ads: we may use a third-party vendor to serve content and advertisements on our website, which may use cookies, as noted above. The use of cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet.

Retargeting Ads: from time to time, we may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies like Google, Facebook, or [Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/carrotsncake/?hl=en), in order to market the website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the website. You can find out more about their usage of cookies by locating their privacy policy.

## Sponsored Posts & Affiliate Programs Disclosure

In order for me to support my business, I may receive monetary compensation or other types of remuneration for my endorsement, recommendation, testimonial and/or link to any products or services from this blog.

For your convenience, this website may provide hyperlinks to websites and servers maintained by third parties. Carrotsncake.com does not control, evaluate, endorse or guarantee content found in such sites. Carrotsncake.com does not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, services or content of these sites or the parties that operate them. You should carefully review their privacy statements and other conditions of use. Your use of these sites is entirely at your own risk.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
